RANDY L. ADAMS, CFA, CPA

504 Springwood Lane Bolingbrook, IL 60440-1477 630/226-0478 (land), 630/337-6874 (cell) RandyL.Adams@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

MBA, CFA, and CPA with extensive and progressive portfolio management and securities analysis experience. Experience includes portfolio management of diversified fixed income portfolios and large cap growth equities, credit analysis of municipal and corporate issuers, and equity analysis of small and mid cap companies. Present and past responsibilities include screening for securities candidates, analyzing financial and regulatory filings, and determining inclusion within the portfolios. Self-directed, task-oriented, and results-focused with strong analytical and communication skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BANKNOTE CAPITAL CORPORATION, Inverness, Illinois

2008 - Present

A service company providing management, accounting, investment, and tax assistance to six affiliated community banks located in Colorado, New Mexico, Virginia, and Wisconsin.

Chief Investment Officer

Assisting the community banks in fixed income management, credit research, and asset/liability management. Positioned as an investment resource for the banks. Managing \$408.5 million (12/31/2010) of fixed income securities for six community banks as the designated investment officer. Preparing periodic market updates and evaluating opportunities for distribution among the banks. Consulting with the banks to implement a mix of asset categories and portfolio strategies. Executing all trade purchases and sales of securities on the behalf of the banks through a network of approved broker/dealers. Updating and expanding the banks' Investment Policy Statements to incorporate relevant regulatory constraints, bank-specific limitations, market opportunities, and financial/tax objectives. Delivering periodic presentations to the banks' Boards of Directors and senior management teams on market conditions and opportunities available for investment. Responsible for internally-generated credit research on newly purchased and currently held securities. Providing quarterly Other-Than-Temporary-Impairment ("OTTI") evaluations of selected securities per guidelines promulgated by ASC 320-10-35. Providing input to the banks' Asset/Liability Committees and Investment Committees, including contributions to Asset/Liability Management Policies, Interest Rate Risk Policies, Liquidity Management Policies, and Contingent Funding Policies. Assisting the banks' asset/liability modeling and providing commentary on assumptions used. Counseling the affiliated banks' Profit Sharing Plan Committee regarding current and prospective mutual fund choices. Advising bank ownership on wealth management concerns such as marketable equity security reviews, private equity opportunities, asset allocation changes, and diversification of concentrated stock positions. Managing the Investment Associate position with straight-line reporting through setting of nearterm objectives & long-term goals, coaching, and providing periodic performance evaluations.

- Expanding asset categories utilized by the banks to include corporate bonds, private-label mortgage-backed securities, trust preferred securities, and taxable municipal bonds along with the prior usage of Treasury securities, agency debentures & mortgage-backed securities, and tax-exempt municipal bonds.
- Overseeing +65.7% growth of the banks' securities portfolios as the banks' assets expanded +9.0% from year-end 2008 to year-end 2010.

MORGAN STANLEY and CO., Chicago, Illinois

2006 - 2008

Global investment bank offering investment advisory services through its Private Wealth Management unit.

Vice President and Investment Representative

Marketed and managed diversified portfolios of equities, fixed income, and alternatives on an open architecture platform. Serviced client base comprised of endowments, foundations, and high net worth individuals. Developed, marketed, and managed Large/Mid-Cap Domestic Core Equity solution benchmarked to S&P 500 and Russell 1000 Growth indices. Responsible for security analysis resulting in buy, hold, and sell decisions. Held Series 7 and 66 licenses.

- Exceeded the benchmarks with a return of +12.74% versus S&P 500's +4.83% and Russell 1000 Growth's +10.51%.
- Utilizing a self-developed quantitative/statistical model, successfully created and managed a Hedge Fund of Funds replication strategy with convertibles, options, ETFs, and preferred stock securities.

Randy Adams Page 2

THE NORTHERN TRUST COMPANY, Chicago, Illinois

1996 - 2006

A Chicago-based bank emphasizing trust and investment management services to individuals and institutions.

Vice President and Portfolio Manager

Managed \$875 million of assets with \$4.1 million of revenues. Oversaw portfolios of stocks and bonds for institutional and high net-worth clients, advising on asset allocation, risk management, and tax management. Analyzed companies' financial characteristics and valued securities for purchase, retention, or sale in discretionary portfolios. Assisted with new business development efforts for personal trusts, agencies, private foundations, charitable trusts, and IRAs. Serviced a diverse set of demanding clients through presentations, telephone calls, e-mails, and letters. Covered health care sector as liaison among portfolio manager peers, internal research analysts, and sell-side research.

- Achieved successful long-term track record for large cap growth equity portfolios benchmarked to the S&P 500. Annualized return of +8.37% vs. S&P's +8.33% and Russell 1000 Growth's +4.89%.
- Evaluated and selected health care stocks for the model portfolio ("Best Ideas Portfolio"). Annualized total return of +7.01% vs. S&P 500 Health's +3.93%.
- Promoted from Second Vice President in 2001.

SECURITIES CORPORATION OF IOWA (acquired by Wells Fargo in 2001)

1994 - 1996

A full-service brokerage firm with offices in Cedar Rapids, IA, Waterloo, IA, and Chicago, IL.

Assistant Vice President - Research

Provided mid-cap and small-cap stock purchase ideas based upon fundamental analysis to account executives. Covered 15-20 issues in several industries, issued specific Buy-Hold-Sell ratings, and created earnings estimates. Prepared written company research reports for both internal and public distribution. Assisted with the compilation of Monthly Statistical Summary and Model Equity Portfolio newsletters. Developed business through periodic discussions with institutional clients and prospects.

- Achieved solid performance. Buy-rated stocks had an annualized total return of +23.76% vs. S&P 400 MidCap's +23.44% and S&P 600 SmallCap's +23.22%.
- Promoted the firm's research through *Investor's Business Daily, Barron's, Dow Jones News, The Des Moines Register*, and Cedar Rapids Gazette.

FIRSTAR CORPORATION (acquired by U.S. Bancorp in 2001)

1989 - 1994

A Midwest bank holding company headquartered in Milwaukee, WI with an investment management subsidiary.

Investment Officer and Portfolio Manager, Des Moines, Iowa (1992-1994)

Firstar Investment Research and Management Company (FIRMCO)

Active retention of clients through quarterly or semi-annual meetings to review objectives, strategy, and performance returns. Managed \$205 million of taxable and tax-exempt portfolios through asset allocation and security selection. Developed new business with trust officers by discussing stock selection philosophy and performance record with prospects.

- Going beyond stated responsibilities, researched small and mid cap stock candidates for inclusion into the common trust funds and Portico mutual funds.
- Assisted with the successful integration of the acquired Banks of Iowa trust activities into the Firstar system and overcoming client skepticism.

Trust Investment Officer, Firstar Bank, Cedar Rapids, Iowa (1989-1992)

Managed nearly \$30 million of personal trusts, agencies, conservatorships, and employee benefit plans. Analyzed large cap stock candidates for inclusion to internal working list of approved purchases. Analyzed municipal issuers of General Obligation and Revenue bonds to determine sufficiency of interest coverage. Participated in the bank's Asset Review Committee as a member. Registered Representative (Series 6 and 63) of Elan Investment Services, a brokerage subsidiary.

• Promoted from Trust Investment Administrator in 1991.

UNIVERSITY of ILLINOIS at CHICAGO

2001 - Present

Department of Finance, College of Business Administration

Adjunct Lecturer of Finance (part-time)

Taught semester-length finance courses comprised of 40-60 graduates (MBA candidates) or undergraduates. Responsible for course preparation, syllabus specifics, and lecture materials. Evaluated and graded students' assignments, projects, mid-terms, and final examinations.

- Taught Finance 300 Investments. Topics included organization of security markets; legal and institutional environment; mechanics of trading; financial intermediation; security classifications; and general principles of asset valuation with applications to specific securities.
- Taught Finance 430 Introduction to Money and Banking. Topics included balance sheet and income statement aspects

Randy Adams Page 3

of financial institutions; role of the Federal Reserve System; process of reserve banking; activities within the Fed Funds market; mechanics of repurchase agreements; usage of the Discount Window; and current status of risk management tools.

- Taught Finance 431 *Theory and Structure of the Financial Markets*. Topics included examination of depository and non-depository institutions; differences of roles among financial markets participants; regulatory oversight of depository and non-depository participants; various risks facing participants (liquidity, credit, market, forex, etc.); and tools/tactics to manage risk.
- Taught Finance 500 MBA Introduction to Corporate Finance. Topics included theory of corporate finance; goal of the firm; time value of money; investment decisions under certainty and uncertainty; net present value and alternate methodologies; capital budgeting criteria; aspects of the capital markets; and corporate financing decisions.

EDUCATION and PROFESSION ACCREDITATIONS

MBA, Accounting/Marketing, University of Chicago, Graduate School of Business

BBA, Finance, University of Iowa, College of Business Administration

Chartered Financial Analyst

Certified Public Accountant (Illinois)